<note to graders: this resume is out of date and is only for demonstration purposes>

Heather A. Crawford

3802 S Greenwich Ln, Independence, MO 64055 (816) 606-6599 heather.crawford@cerner.com

Summary

High achieving and self-motivated education professional with ample experience in client support, learning development, training, project planning, leading, and creative problem solving. Possesses seven years of experience integrating social and professional communication skills to facilitate teaching, planning, and leading. Worked for two years supporting Cerner clients at the Help Desk.

Highlights

- Experience building curriculum and implementing lesson plans.
- Creates, revises, and implements learning materials and courses.
- Uses diagnostic, formative, and summative assessments to evaluate performance.
- Demonstrates an understanding of learning methodologies backed up with evidence-based reasoning.
- Trains adult learners in best practices and material implementation.

Experience

2019-Current Cerner Help Desk Lee's Summit, MO

Senior Support Analyst

- Received an Outstanding rating on first and current 18-month review.
- Led and developed client training for Help Desk staff supporting East Jefferson Hospital.
- ♦ Obtained Subject Matter Expert role supporting several clients of various sizes and complexity.
- Supported staff members as a role coach and mentor.
- Received Senior Support Analyst title after first 18-month review.
- Constantly communicated with leads to fulfill needs for extra projects to support clients as needed.

2017-2019 Frontier STEM High School Kansas City, MO

10th grade English Teacher; Journalism Teacher

- Awards received for student growth and mastery.
- Over 80% of student scores exceeded state testing expectations.
- Led professional development modules training adults to increase critical thinking skills.
- Developed excellent personal relationships and communication skills to provide students and parents with a smooth environment for learning.
- Developing critical thinking plans to resolve errors in student workflow and encourage growth.

2014-2017

Norborne High School

Norborne, MO

9-12 English Teacher

- ♦ 100% of students scored at or higher than expectation levels on state assessments
- Organized community events for holiday and academic achievement celebrations with record setting attendance.
- ❖ Managed fund-raising for Pennies-for-Patients; earning a record \$1,500.
- Served in a leadership role for the Positive Behavior Intervention and Support committee, developing behavior plans school wide.

2013-2014 Raytown South High School Raytown, MO

Instructional Assistant

- Organized a new record-keeping system that organized classified information in a more secure and efficient manner.
- ❖ Increased student achievement level for all 12 individualized students plans.

Education

Bachelors in Secondary English Education from the University of Missouri- Kansas City